baptisthealth.net 2008-12-18

# Website Privacy Policy

**Website Privacy Policy**

Baptist Health South Florida, Inc. ("Baptist Health South Florida" or "Baptist Health") respects your personal privacy and is committed to adhering to federal and state privacy laws and industry guidelines for using personal information collected from this web site in order to protect you and your identity. This privacy policy describes how we handle the personal information that you provide to us on this web site and is collected by us from this website. This policy applies only to the **www.baptisthealth.net** Website (the "Baptist Health Website" or the "Website") and not to any other third party web sites that may be accessible from here. 

After reading this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into and is a part of this Website's Terms and Conditions, you will know: 

  1. what information Baptist Health collects from you; 
  2. how Baptist Health uses your information; 
  3. what choices you have about how Baptist Health treats your information; 
  4. how Baptist Health protects your privacy; 
  5. what Baptist Health does about children visiting this Website; 
  6. how you can contact Baptist Health. 

Please be sure to read this Privacy Policy before using this Website or submitting information to us through this Website. Our privacy policies may change from time to time and your continued use of this Website is acceptance of such changes, so please check this area periodically for updates to this Policy. 

  1. **Information Baptist Health Collects from You** _top_  
 **Active Information Collection**  
Like many other websites, we actively collect information from our visitors both by asking specific questions on this Website and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail. Some of the information that you submit through this Website may be personally identifiable (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, etc.). 

**Passive Information Collection**  
As you navigate through a website, certain information can be passively collected from the website (that is, gathered without you actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as navigational data collection. Like most webssite operators, Baptist Health tracks IP addresses, use both session and persistent cookies, and assigns Internet tags. Our system also automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on this Website and collects operational information about the technology you use, such as your browser, type of computer, operating systems, and Internet service providers. We passively collect information from this Website to understand what areas of this Website are most popular, which areas may require improvement, and what technologies are being used by our visitors. This information helps us to update and improve this Website. We also use this information for security purposes, to detect and to block security breaches and to provide you with a safe online environment. 

  2. **How Baptist Health Uses your Information** _top_  
Baptist Health uses your personal information that is collected from this Website to enhance the operation of this Website and allow you to use all of its features. Baptist Health may contact you about new features or products in which it believes you may be interested. Baptist Health may disclose your personal information to the reputable vendors that assist us in processing information or operating this Website. These vendors are restricted from using the information for any purpose other than helping us to provide products and services. Baptist Health may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, online traffic patterns and related information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information. Baptist Health also will disclose any information that it is required to disclose by law or by an appropriate government authority. 
  3. **Choices You Have about How Baptist Health Uses your Information** _top_  
We strive to provide you with as many choices and as much control as possible regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 

You may send us an e-mail message addressed to the Web Coordinator at [corporatepr@baptisthealth.net](mailto:corporatepr@baptisthealth.net) or call us at **786-596-6534** , to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. To protect your privacy, we will only respond to e-mail messages that you send to us by responding to that same e-mail account unless you provide us with an alternative means to communicate with you. Should you elect to have your information deleted, we will also delete your user account. 

If you do not wish us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties, please tell the Web Coordinator at [corporatepr@baptisthealth.net](mailto:corporatepr@baptisthealth.net). You may also opt out of receiving marketing messages from Baptist Health by notifying us at the same address. 

If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of this Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly. 

You should review this Privacy Policy carefully, because if you do not agree with our practices, your ultimate choice is not to use this Website. Remember, by using any part of this Website, you accept and agree to our privacy practices. If we update this Privacy Policy, your continued use of this Website (following the posting of the revised policy) means that you accept and agree to the terms of the revised privacy policy. 

  4. **How Baptist Health Protects your Information** _top_  
We work hard to protect your personal information. We use both technical and procedural methods to maintain the integrity and security of our databases, including the SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption which provides a level of security and privacy for all data sent over the Internet. The SSL connection method provides a mechanism for determining whether the data has been altered in transit. Baptist Health also protects information by using an Internet firewall. The Internet firewall is a security mechanism that allows us to restrict access to our network from the Internet, allowing approved traffic in and out according to Baptist Health's thought-out plan. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. If you have access to password-protected features, never share your password with anyone else, notify us promptly if you believe your password security has been breached, and remember to log off of this Website before you leave your computer. 

This Website contains links to other Websites operated by third parties that may be of interest to you. We cannot control these third party Websites, which may collect personal information from you. When you follow a link and leave this Website, you do so at your own risk. 

  5. **What Baptist Health Does about Children Visiting this Website** _top_  
This Website is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from Website visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose online. 
  6. **How You can Contact Baptist Health** _top_  
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Website, please contact the **Web Coordinator** at:  
 **Baptist Health South Florida, Inc.  
6855 Red Road, Suite 500  
Telephone: 305-596-6534  
E-mail: corporate@baptisthealth.net**

|   
---|---
